Contact

941-221-9300 (Mobile) chantelhillrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chantel-allen-4775234a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Microsoft Office

Certifications

CEN

CCRN

Cardiac Surgery (Adult) (CSC)
Cardiac Medicine (Adult) (CMC)
CCRN, CEN

Chantel Allen

RN BSN, CCRN-CMC-CSC, CEN at Johns Hopkins All Children's Hospital

Saint Petersburg, Florida

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the medical practice industry. Skilled in Nonprofit Organizations, Microsoft Excel, Clinical Research, Customer Service, and Microsoft Word. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelors of Science in Nursing focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Graceland University.

Experience

Johns Hopkins All Children's Hospital RN BSN, CCRN-CMC-CSC, CEN March 2020 - Present (5 months) St Petersburg, Florida, United States

PEDS CVICU:-)

CVICU RN RN, BSN, CCRN, CEN, EMTP 2016 - Present (4 years) Southwest Florida

NCH Healthcare System RN, BSN, CCRN on CVRU May 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 1 month) Naples, Florida

CCRN on CVRU

Venice Regional Medical Ctr CVICU CCRN September 2016 - August 2017 (1 year) Bayfront - Venice

Open Heart ICU

Tampa General Hospital

RN, CCRN, CEN,EMTP in the CTICU October 2016 - March 2017 (6 months)

Tampa, Florida

Fawcett Memorial Hospital
CVICU CCRN
September 2016 - March 2017 (7 months)
Port Charlotte, Florida

Open Heart ICU

Henry Ford Health System
SICU RN at Henry Ford Medical Systems
August 2015 - July 2016 (1 year)
Detroit, MI

Contract through Medical Solutions then direct hire through Henry Ford BestChoice In-House System Critical Care Float Pool.

Medical Solutions
CVICU/SICU CCRN at Sparrow Health System
August 2015 - July 2016 (1 year)
Lansing, Michigan

Contracted at Sparrow and Henry Ford Hospital

Aureus Medical Group CICU/MICU at Northern Michigan Medical Center March 2015 - July 2015 (5 months) Petoskey, Michigan

Contract ICU RN at Northern Michigan Medical Center

Hurley Medical Center RN, BSN, CCRN, CEN, EMTP 2006 - March 2015 (9 years) Neuro Trauma ICU

Neuro Trauma 100

Neuro Trauma ICU RN in Flint, MI

Concord EMS, Toledo Hospital, EMTS Monroe. Critical Care Transport RN/Paramedic, EMTP April 1992 - September 2005 (13 years 6 months) South West Michigan. Greater Detroit Area. Northern Ohio.

Education

Graceland University

Bachelors of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2002 - 2005)

University of New York, Regents
ASN, Associates of Science of Nursing (2000 - 2002)

Hurley School of Paramedics
Paramedic Certification · (1991 - 1992)